<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>connectagram.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="es_PE">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="hr">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Connectagram</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">"Connectagram"</name>
  <summary>Unscramble words placed in patterns</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Rozluštěte slova umístěná ve vzorech</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Entschlüsselte Wörter in Mustern anordnen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Αποκρυπτογραφήσετε λέξεις poz τοποθετήθηκαν σε μοτίβα</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es_PE">Descrifrar palabras colocadas en patrones</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Déchiffrage de mots reliés entre eux</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Menata-lagi huruf teracak dalam pola</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Riordina le parole disposte in schemi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Iššifruokite šablone išdėstytus žodžius</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Orden de verhaspelde woorden in patronen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Rozszyfrowanie słów umieszczonych w wzorach</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Reordena palavras dispostas em padrões</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Ordonaţi cuvinte plasate în tipare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Kalıplarda yerleştirilmiş kelimeleri düzenle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Розшифруйте слова, що знаходяться у відповідних комірках</summary>

  <description>
    <p>Connectagram is a word unscrambling game. The board consists of several scrambled words that are joined together. You can choose the length of the words, the amount of words, and the pattern that the words are arranged in. The game provides a hint option for times when you are stuck, and features an online word lookup that fetches the definitions of each word from Wiktionary. Your current progress is automatically saved.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Connectagram ist ein Wortangramm Spiel. Das Spiel besteht aus mehreren verschlüsselten Wörtern, die miteinander verbunden sind. Sie können die Länge der Wörter, die Menge der Wörter, und das Muster, in den die Wörter angeordnet sind wählen. Das Spiel bietet eine Hinweisoption für die Verzögerung, wenn Sie stecken geblieben sind, und verfügt über eine Online-Wort-Suche, die die Definitionen der einzelnen Begriffe aus Wiktionary abruft. Ihr aktueller Fortschritt wird automatisch gespeichert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Connectagram είναι ενα παιχνίδι αποκωδικοποίησης λέξεων.  Ο πίνακας αποτελείται από πολλά κωδικοποιημένα λόγια που ενώνονται μεταξύ τους. Μπορείτε να επιλέξετε το μήκος των λέξεων, το ποσό των λέξεων, και το μοτίβο που οι λέξεις διατάσσονται. Το παιχνίδι προσφέρει μια επιλογή υποδειξεων για τους χρόνους όταν δεν μπορείτε να ξεκολλήσετε, και διαθέτει μια ηλεκτρονική αναζήτηση λέξεων που φέρνει τους ορισμούς της κάθε λέξης από το Βικιλεξικό. Η πρόοδός σας αποθηκεύεται αυτόματα.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es_PE">Connectagram es un juego para descifrar palabras. El tablero se compone de varias palabras revueltas que se unen entre sí. Se puede elegir la longitud de las palabras, la cantidad de palabras, y el patrón en que las palabras se organizan. El juego ofrece una opción de sugerencia para los momentos cuando está estancado y cuenta con una búsqueda de textos en línea que recupera las definiciones de cada palabra de Wiktionary. Su actual progreso se guarda automáticamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Connectagram est un jeu de déchiffrage de mots. Le plateau consiste en plusieurs mots brouillés reliés les uns aux autres. Vous avez le choix de la longueur des mots, de leur nombre et de la figure dans laquelle ils sont arrangés. Le jeu propose une option d'aide en cas de blocage, ainsi qu'une recherche en ligne des définitions de chaque mot sur Wiktionary. Votre progression en cours est automatiquement sauvegardée. </p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Connectagram adalah game pengurai kata. Papan terdiri dari beberapa kata acak yang digabungkan menjadi satu.Anda dapat memilih panjang kata, jumlah kata, dan pola pengaturan kata tersebut.Permainan ini menyediakan opsi petunjuk saat Anda macet, dan menampilkan pencarian kata daring yang mengambil definisi setiap kata dari Wiktionary. Kemajuan Anda saat ini disimpan secara otomatis.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Connectagram è un gioco di decodifica. Il tabellone è composto da diverse parole confuse che sono unite insieme. Puoi scegliere la lunghezza delle parole, la quantità di parole e il modello in cui sono disposte le parole. Il gioco offre un'opzione di suggerimento per i momenti in cui sei bloccato e presenta una ricerca di parole online che recupera le definizioni di ogni parola da Wikizionario. I tuoi progressi attuali vengono salvati automaticamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Connectagram yra žodžių iššifravimo žaidimas. Plokštė susideda iš kelių, kartu sujungtų užšifruotų žodžių. Galite pasirinkti žodžių ilgį, skaičių ir šabloną, pagal kurį žodžiai bus išdėstyti. Žaidime yra užuominos funkciją skirta tam atvejui, kai užstrigsite aklavietėje, o taip pat yra žodžių peržiūra su kiekvieno žodžio apibrėžtimi iš Vikižodyno. Jūsų dabartinio žaidimo eiga yra automatiškai įrašoma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Connectagram is een woord orden spel. Het bord bestaat uit diverse verhaspelde woroden die samengevoegd zijn. Je kunt de lengte, het aantal en het patroon van de woorden kiezen. Het spel heeft een hint optie voor als je vast komt te zitten en de mogelijkheid om de definities van woorden on-line op te zoeken van Wiktionary. Je voortgang is automatisch opgeslagen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Connectagram to gra w właściwe poukładanie slow. Gra składa się z kilku zakodowanych słów, które są połączone ze sobą. Możesz wybrać długość słów, ilość słów i wzór, w którym słowa będą umieszczone. Gra oferuje opcję podpowiedzi w monecie, gdy utkniesz, i dysponuje wyszukiwaniem słów online, które pobiera definicje każdego słowa z Wikisłownika. Automatyczny zapis twojego postępu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Connectagram é jogo de reordenar palavras. O tabuleiro concste em várias palavras desordenadas que estão ligadas. Pode escolher o comprimento das palavras, a quantidade de palavras e o padrão em que as palavras estão dispostas. O jogo fornece uma dica opcional para alturas que estiver sem soluções, e disponibiliza as definições de cada palavra obtidas da Internet provenientes do Wikcionário. O progresso atual é gravado automaticamente.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Connectagram este un joc de ordonare cuvinte. Tabela este constituită din mai multe cuvinte amestecate, care sunt unite împreună. Puteţi alege lungimea cuvintelor, cantitatea de cuvinte, şi tiparul după care cuvintele sînt aranjate. Jocul oferă o opţiune de sugestie pentru momentele în care v-aţi blocat, şi o căutare cuvînt online care preia definiţiile fiecărui cuvînt de la Wikţionar. Progresul curent este salvat automat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Connectagram bir kelime çözme oyunu. Pano birkaç şifreli kelimelerin birlikte katılımıyla oluşur. Kelimelerin uzunluğunu, kelimelerin miktarını ve kelimelerin düzenlendiği deseni seçebilirsiniz. Oyun, sıkıştığınız zamanlar için bir ipucu seçeneği sunar ve her kelimenin Vikisözlük'ten tanımlamalarını getiren çevrimiçi bir kelime araması içerir. Mevcut ilerlemeniz otomatik olarak kaydedilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">"Connectagram" - це гра, де потрібно розшифровувати слова. Гральна дошка складається з декількох зашифрованих слів, які поєднані разом. Ви в змозі обирати довжину слів, кількість слів та модель розташування цих слів. У грі є можливість отримання підказки, якщо у вас виникли труднощі з розшифровкою, а також можливість перегляду значення розгаданих слів за допомогою "Wiktionary". Ваш поточний поступ зберігається автоматично.</p>
  </description>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://gottcode.org/connectagram/screenshots/appdata.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://gottcode.org/connectagram/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://gottcode.org/connectagram/bugs/</url>
  <url type="donation">https://gottcode.org/tip/</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/projects/p/connectagram/</url>

  <update_contact>graeme@gottcode.org</update_contact>

  <translation type="qt">connectagram</translation>

  <provides>
    <binary>connectagram</binary>
  </provides>

  <kudos>
    <kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
    <kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
  </kudos>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.2.11" date="2020-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Did not load locales with underscores</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Italian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.10" date="2019-08-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Window icon didn't work in Wayland</li>
          <li>Improved loading locales</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.9" date="2018-07-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Automatic high DPI support</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.8" date="2018-06-22">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>FIXED: Missing launcher icon in Linux</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="1.2.7" date="2018-05-29">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Replaced deprecated code</li>
          <li>Extra warnings only shown in debug build</li>
          <li>Improved Linux deployment</li>
          <li>Improved macOS deployment</li>
          <li>Improved Windows deployment</li>
          <li>Translation updates: Portuguese, Ukrainian</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
